

ABOUT ME

Over the last 6 years of experience I have worked in my owned shop, where as a graphic designer i have completed numerous projects for clients in the past. I am proficient in Adobe Photoshop, and Illustrator and can easily create logos, brochures, banners, tarpaulins, and other visuals. In addition I am a computer technician widely experienced in simulation via finite elements method and computer aided.

SKILLS

- BluePrism
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Canva
- Visual Design
- CorelDraw

CERTIFICATION

Certificate of Completion Home Base Connect

February 24, 2023
• Facebook Ads

- Shopify
- Social Media Management
- Virtual Assistant
- WordPress Freelancing

Certificate of Participation STYAVA

March 7 2023

• Integrated In House AI Models in Power Platform

Certificate of Completion XciTech DXC Technology December 16, 2022

• Blue Prism RPA (Robotics Process Automation)

Certification of Completion
Pomona Institute in Technology Inc.
June 8 2017

• Visual Graphic Designer

Certification of Completion Endonnella Institute of Technology Inc. January 10 2013

Computer Hardware Servicing

ANNA MARICE EBEN BOYOSE

GRAPHIC ARTIST

+639 4554 27 091 +639 6034 82 810

🖄 amboyose27@gmail.com

MY PORTFOLIO:

https://bamby27.github.io/myportfolio/

WORK EXPERIENCES

Philippine National Police Non Uniformed Personnel - Job Order

September 3, 2018 to Present

Administrative Staff/ Database Administrator/ Graphic Design

- Prepares memorandum letters and other requirements for administrative matters;
- Maintains and up-to-date list of records and recommends measures necessary to ensure proper filing indexing of all files;
- Maintenance troubleshoot in technical computers, LAN/WAN configurations, including routing & switching;
- Inventories of hardware and software components; and
- Can do visual graphic design, can create logos or manipulate photos using software applications.

Kirobin Digital Printing

January 2016 to 2018

Graphic Designer/ Computer Technician

- Create visually appealing designs and layouts in print media;
- Designing products on corporate graphic design for the company;
- Visualizing and creating graphics including illustrations ,logos, layouts and photos; and
- Maintaining computer systems, troubleshooting errors, and repairing the organization's hardware

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MINDANAO Bachelor of Science in Criminology |

January 2007-December 2013 (Undergrad)

Study of crime and criminal behavior, informed by principles of sociology and other non-legal fields.

POMONA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY INC.

Visual Graphic Designer National Certificate III June 2016 | 368 Hours

Study in graphic design, and work in interface design, motion graphics packaging or any using software applications.

ENDONELLA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY INC.

Computer Hardware Servicing National Certificate III January 2013 | 380 Hours

Study in computer install, configure and maintain computer systems and networks, diagnosis and troubleshooting of computer systems, as well as in the performance of computer operations